I just binge watched years and years and
they're probably gonna be spoilers in
this video so if you don't like spoilers
go watch it and then come back and let's
start a freaking revolution but I'm not
going to not do spoilers
cuz we need a revolution more than we
need media to not be spoiled in the show
they it's a family it's I just looked up
a description and it says it's like this
is us meets black mirror it's pretty app
description and this family goes through
a decade of these incremental changes
happening in the UK and Europe and the
world and none of it is far-fetched not
a single incident is far-fetched it is
the world we're living towards and a lot
of the crisis ease we are currently
facing are only gonna get worse I know
this is why I'm creating about a world
our refugee crisis is good is going to
get worse environmental damage and
flooding and weather events are going to
get worse and the amount of effect
poverty has is going to get worse this
family is upper-middle class and you can
see how devastated they are by the
events of the future imagine already
being lower-class when they start
imagine not having your papers in the UK
when they start not that they don't
touch on that our choice as everyday
citizens as the people of this world is
whether we're going to watch our world
get incrementally worse in a way that
never sparks a revolution and if it does
is going to be violent and chaotic and
no real change will come or we can get
incrementally better we can choose to
not leave anybody behind to create the
systems that make it so we're not
leaving it up to our governments who are
going to get worse and worse at doing
jobs that are more and more complex
the world is going to get concentrated
into more and more more and more of the
powers and country into smaller and
smaller hands of corporations mainly
technology companies
we're already allowing that to happen
because we're choosing to take the
incremental benefits with the horrific
incremental cost the cost of human
suffering and slavery and environmental
degradation and we all feel the effects
we're scapegoating each other
dealing with this surface level of
hatred and fear instead of actually
solving the problems and together we can
solve the problems we can collect the
information that we need to understand
and solve the problems instead of just
allowing all the information to exist
online and making it more and more
difficult to be able to pick and pick
the actual truth out and then yelling at
people that they're getting dumber and
dumber no the world's getting more and
more complex and we need infinitely
better systems to understand it and they
have to work for everyone we need to
create the technology to allow us to
collaborate on a massive scale we have
to create the technology that helps us
witness each other's catastrophes
because the issue is that each
individual experiencing catastrophe
getting cancer being deported having
their government torture them is not
witnessed and it's a one-off
it can easily be just seen as as facts
and figures instead of that person's
life that person's misery that we all
could have helped stop and so we have a
choice right now we can leave it up to
the powers that be that we always have
voting new governments that aren't going
to do fuck-all about any of it
or we can start taking control start
realizing that it's there is no them
that's gonna solve it just like there's
no them that's causing it we are causing
it and we need to solve it we need to
to choose how to get our needs met in
the economy without causing suffering we
need to be able to live lives that we
thrive in that we have an abundance of
resources without making it so no one
else can have that we can live a life
that is Omni when we can live a life or
when everybody every person who has
their needs met has their health has has
food has clean water has electricity
knows that they don't have to worry
about themselves and their children is
an asset to humanity and everyone that's
allowed to fall through the cracks can
be a weapon against us a weapon against
the system or just go invisible I don't
want that option I want the option of
being able to come together and make it
incrementally better asking how can I
help you as an individual and creating
the social media that connects us
instead of divides us where we can
directly help each other we're not
leaving our social safety nets up to
governments who are clearly not there to
help pull us out of poverty or they
would have done it already
we can pull ourselves out of poverty
without a top-down charity approach but
a let's figure out how we feed ourselves
approach let's figure out how we get our
transportation needs met and then
inviting every single person to come who
wants to none of it has to be done by
force every piece of it can be voluntary
and fun and enjoyable and meeting the
individual where they're at and so I
wanted to come on here and do this video
as soon as I had finished binge-watching
years two years because I felt called -
we are creating the technology
cooperative here and there are so many
people creating amazing projects and
working in their own lives their own
communities creating amazing things and
we're able to bring any amount of that
together the power is exponential
and we unleash all of humanity on it
when it can be as easy as going on
social media to help improve the world
to help make the world more informed and
have power spread out instead of in the
hands of a few you get power over your
own life and you get to be empowered in
groups to have to make systems that work
for you we get incrementally better
until the tipping point when it's gonna
look like utopia it's gonna look like a
world we can tell our grandchildren we
were part of Micky and everybody's
invited everybody's invited at whatever
point it calls to them right now we're
looking for massive co-operators people
who can see what a beautiful world we
can create with cooperation if that's
not you yet if you are skeptical that's
okay you'll see it start you'll see us
start to make the tools once you feel
the spark then you can come on board and
we keep proving it to each other
we'll keep proving to each other that
we're in it we want to cooperate we want
to give ourselves little bits of our
labor little bits of our ingenuity
little bits of our passion and
collectively create something amazing
and as we do that the amazing thing
calls it everyone else and every new
person brings with them their passion
their data their connections so we
create an anti rivalries society one
where I can see that helping you helps
me why wouldn't I want to help you then
we've been taught the opposite and we
are complex creatures we are both
competitive and cooperative we cannot
kill the competitive part we cannot kill
the cooperative part all we can do is
allow for that and incentivize the
cooperation incentivize without
penalizing the competition
allowing people to come and give their
best selves and say what's not working
and make it better make it easier to
understand it make it simple for
everybody's vast diversity and abilities
we can create a world that works for
every one of us who's in please like and
subscribe please share this video invite
everyone because everyone is invited and
nobody is forced to join we can create a
world that works for everyone a better
world is on its way and you all get to
be part of creating it thank you